Yes?
なお (菜緒)はーい
Yuri.
ゆりりん!?
What's wrong? You're soaking wet.
どうしたの? びしょ濡れだよ
What happened to you?
どうしたんだよ
Uehara...
(EB) aia...
I'm getting a divorce.
私離婚する
So... what is it this time?
(上原) ...で今度は何?
Probably just another fight with my brother over something stupid.
どうせまた兄貴と くつだらねーことで
Something like he didn't notice you changed your hair,
髪形変えたのに 気づかないとか
or he ate some fried chicken you were saving for yourself.
楽しみに残しておいた から揚げ食われたとか
They've always fought over dumb stuff.
もう昔っから しようもねーことばっかだから
It's a waste of time to worry about them.
心配するだけ損するぞ
-But-- -Nao,
(菜緒)でも (百合)菜緒ちゃん
I'm sorry, but can I stay here for a while?
悪いんだけどちょっとの間 泊めてもらえないかな?
Sure, of course. That's fine.
うんもちろん いいよ
Thank you.
佰合)ありがとう
Hey. This is my house too, you know.
おい俺の家でもあるんだぞ
Please, may I?
お願い
What the heck happened between you?
何があったんだよ つにんに
Takuya...
佰合) してた
He's been...
卓也
having an affair.
浮気
-What? -Really?
はあ!? (菜緒)えっ えつ
There's no way in hell my brother--
んなわけねーだろ? あの兄貴が
Yes he has! That's why...
してたの!だから
I'm getting a divorce.
私離婚します!
But...
ちょっ... ちよつ…
I'm going to talk with my brother. I'll sleep over there tonight.
俺ちょっと兄貴と話してくる 今日は泊まってくるから
OK.
(菜緒) うん
-Take care of Yuri for me. -OK, I will.
(上原)百合のこと頼むな (菜緒) うん分かった
-Here. -Thanks.
はい は上原)おう 仩原)おう
Take care.
いってらっしゃい
I can't believe this. An affair? Totally impossible.
ったく何なんだよ浮気って... マジありえねー
That brother of mine would never have an affair.
あの兄貴が 浮気するわけないだろ
Oh, that's hot!
うーんあっつい
I really can't believe... That's hot!
(百合)浮気とか本当. あっつい!
...that he had an affair.
ありえないんだけど
I wonder if Yuri really is going to get a divorce.
ゆりりん 本当に離婚しちゃうのかな
Hold on a second.
ちょっと待って
If that really does happen...
もしも本当に そうなっちゃつたら
Uehara will...
上原君…
I thought... I'd gotten over you...
俺お前のこと 吹っ切れたと思ってたけど
but if you're leaving my brother, that changes things.
兄貴と別れるなら 話は別だな
Uehara...
久志
I'll make you mine and treat you well our whole lives.
俺はお前を 一生大事にする
OK.
うん
No, no, no!
(菜緒)やだやだやだ そんなのやだ
Oh no! What should I do?
どうしよう どうしたらいいの?
Huh? Yuri?
えつゆりりん!?
Let's... kiss.
チューしよ
Huh?
へ?
I kiss anyone when I'm drunk.
私酔っ払うと 誰にでもキスしちやうんだよね
Is that what's happening?
まさか…
No... Wait, Yuri!
ちょっ…ちょっと待って ゆりりん!
Yuri!
ゆりりん…
I really like you a lot, but not in that way.
私ゆりりんのこと大好きだけど そういう関係は
It's a little soon for that, I mean, it's going too far.
まだ早いっていうか 行きすぎちゃってるんだよ
Oh!
おっ! つ
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Eek!
おっ…ふおおおつ~!
Five times on the cheeks.
ほっぺに5回
Three times on the forehead.
おでこに3回
I just barely covered my mouth.
口はぎりぎりガード
That was close.
危なかった
How pitiful that my second kiss was also in a strange twist of events.
2回目のキスも成り行きなんて 悲しすぎ
Yes?
はーい
Nao, I'm really, really sorry about yesterday.
(百合)菜緒ちゃん 昨日は本当にごめんなさい!
It's totally all right, Yuri.
全然大丈夫だよ ねつゆりりん
Wasn't I all over you last night?
私やらかしちやったんじゃない?
Yikes!
はっ!
I'm seriously going to quit drinking.
もう本気で禁酒する!
Nao, if I try to have a drink,
菜緒ちゃん 私がお酒飲もうとしてたら
knock me flat and bawl me out.
張り倒して 思いっきり叱って
Got it. I'll knock you flat and bawl you out.
分かった つに 張り倒して思いっきり叱る
Thank you. I'll need it.
佰合)ありがとう よろしくお願いします
No problem.
(菜緒)了解しました
There they are.
あいつら...
Oh. Uehara.
(菜緒)あっ上原君だ
-Already in such a bad mood? -Of course I am!
(菜緒)朝から何か不機嫌 (上原)当たり前だろ!
How come neither of you have been answering your phones?
何でお前ら2人して 携帯出ねえんだよ
It made me worry about you.
何かあったかと思うだろうが
Oh, you're right. There's a lot...
本当だ こんなに
I turned my phone off.
私は電源切ってるもんね~
My brother's called you a bunch of times.
兄貴何度も電話してるぞ
Tell him that he doesn't have to.
佰合) "してこなくていいって 言っといてよ
-Tell him yourself. -No way.
自分で言えよ (百合)イヤだ
Why?
(上原)はあ!? I?
Come here. I need to talk to you.
ちょっと来い 話がある
OK, fine. See you later, Nao.
分かったわよ つに 菜緒ちゃんまたねバイバイ!
Yuri's taken off her wedding ring.
(菜緒)結婚指輪外しちやったんだ ゆりりん
Nao... Good morning.
(大地)菜緒 おはよう
Good morning.
おはよう
I like you. I like you, Nao.
好きだよ 俺菜緒のことが好き
-Is that the woman Uehara likes? -Ah! Ah!
上原の好きな奴って (菜緒)あつめ…
Oh, yeah. Marina is waiting for me.
そうだ私 まりなと待ち合わせしてるんだった こった
She asked me to go over the math problems with her.
数学のね問題集 一緒にやろうって言ってて
That stuff's hard, you know. Math is--
あつ深いよね~ 数字って海…
-Morning. What's is it? -Come on. Come with me.
(まりな)おはよう 何? (菜緒)ちょっ…行こう
-Math is calling us. -Huh? What do you mean?
数字が私たちを呼んでるから (まりな)は?何それ
-Nao! -Yes?
菜緒!
I don't have practice today, so let's walk home together.
今日俺部活休みなんだ 一緒に帰ろうぜ
Sorry... but I can't go home with you today.
ごめん 今日は一緒に帰れないから
I'm suspicious.
(光石)怪しい
When Nao panics like that, it always means she's hiding something.
菜緒がパニくってる時って 絶対何か隠してんだよなあ
I'm one reason she's panicking.
俺もパニくらせてる 原因の1つ
Really?
そうなんですか?
I told her I liked her.
菜緒に告つた
Huh?
え?
What... Hold on a second here.
A?ちょ...ちょっと待って ちょっと待って
Daichi told you he liked you?
菜緒大ちゃんに告られたの?
You've got to be kidding.
ウソウソ!
Daichi is an old friend and is like a big brother to her.
大ちゃんは幼なじみで お兄ちゃん的な感じでさ
That kind of thing can turn into love, you know.
そういうのが 恋に変わっていくんだよ
You really think so?
そんなことある?
Just look at us.
俺らがそうだろ
Oh... that's right.
あっっか そ
So, what did you tell him?
でで…で! 菜緒は何て返事したの?
He said, "I don't need an answer."
"返事はいらないって
"I just wanted to tell you that."
“ただ伝えたかっただけだからって
Ahh... Daichi...
はあ…大ちゃん
I can totally feel for him, right here.
(光石)何か俺ここら辺が すげえ切なくなった
Nao, you realize that Uehara's not the only guy around, right?
(まりな)菜緒 上原君だけが男じゃないよ!
I mean, you're not with anyone now,
もうせっかく今 フリーなんだからさ
so maybe you should take Daichi seriously.
大ちゃんのこと意識してみるのも いいんじゃない?
-But, for me, there's only-- -Nao!
でも私の中では 仩原)吉川! よしかわ も上
Uehara.
上原君
Sorry, I've got to go.
ごめんちょっと行ってくる
Nao's head over heels with Uehara for sure.
やっぱ菜緒は 上原君まっしぐらか
But Uehara prefers Yuri, right?
でも上原君は ゆりりんなんだろ? はん
Probably.
たぶん
I think Nao and Daichi would be a great pair, don't you?
俺大地先輩と菜緒って いい感じだと思うんだけどな
I guess so.
まあね
Any way you look at it, Daichi is way kinder too.
どう見ても 大地先輩のほうが優しいだろ
Hmm...
(まりな) うーん
You're going back to your home?
実家に帰る!?
-Yeah. -What?
仩原)ああ (菜緒)えっ
But then, does that mean...
それってもしかして
you're never coming back to our place again?
二度とあの家に 帰ってこないってこと?
-Don't be stupid. Of course I am. -Really?
バーカ んなわけねーだろ (菜緒)え?
Just until this mess with Yuri gets straightened out.
百合のゴタゴタが 片付くまでだよ
Oh, I see.
(菜緒)そっか
Besides, it drives me nuts when she's there.
(上原)何かあいつがいると 調子狂うしな つしな
I'd rather be at my house.
実家のほうがまだマシ
What is it?
どうした?
Nothing.
ううん何でもない
What did your brother say?
お兄さん何て?
He said the affair is a misunderstanding,
ああ浮気は勘違いだって 言ってるけど
but something seems fishy.
何か引っかかんだよな
Hey, I'm really sorry.
っていうか悪い
Getting you involved in my family's personal problems.
身内のことで 吉川にまで迷惑かけて
I don't mind at all. Besides, I really like Yuri.
全然気にしないで 私ゆりりんのこと好きだし
I'm really glad to hear you say that.
そう言ってもらえると マジで助かる
No problem.
(菜緒) うん
Oh, and I didn't make lunch today.
あと私 お弁当今日作れなくて
It's OK. I'll just get something at the canteen.
ああいいよ 購買で何か買うし 貝つ
See you.
じゃあな
"It drives me nuts... when Yuri's there."
"ゆりりんといると 調子狂う,か
Nao!
(大地)菜緒!
Daichi.
大ちゃん
There's somewhere I'd like to take you.
ちょっと付き合ってほしいとこ あるんだけど
Sorry, but I think I told you this morn--
ごめん 私朝も言ったけど
You know, I've done a whole lot of favors for you, Nao.
俺結構菜緒のお願い 聞いてきたと思うんだけどなあ
Yes, that's very true.
はいそのとおりです
-Excellent. OK, let's go. -Huh?
(大地よしじゃあ行こう (菜緒)えっ
What?
えつ
Uehara, kick it back.
(翼)上原君こっちこっち
Wow!
(翼,僚平)すげえ
Wow! It's the Sky Tree.
わあスカイツリーだ!
It's amazing!
すごーい
Daichi, I didn't know you liked sweets.
大ちゃん甘いの好きだっけ?
I was in the mood...
そういう気分だったけど
but just looking at it has made me full.
見ただけで お腹いっぱいになっちゃつた
You're kidding. What a waste!
何それもったいないよ!
-Then you have it, Nao. -What?
ゃあ菜緒が食べろよ (菜緒)えっ じ
No, it's OK. It's yours, Daichi.
いいよ大ちゃんのだし
They say the sundaes here are so marvelous
(大地) ここのパフェ 死ぬ前に一度は のは
that you have to have at least one before you die.
絶対食べたほうがいいって いうぐらい絶品らしいぜ
Yum! This really is delicious.
ん-!本当おいしい
Oh. I'm sorry.
あっごめん
This was yours, but look how much I had.
これ大ちゃんのなのに こんなに食べちゃつた つに
I appreciate the concern, but there's almost none left.
気持ちはうれしいけど ほとんど残ってない
Oh, you're right. Hardly any...
だよね こんなちょっとじゃ..
Here.
(大地)んつ 休地んっ
You have it, Daichi.
大ちゃん食べて
All right, if you insist.
じゃ遠慮なく
It's way too sweet.
甘すぎ
Is Uehara there?
(大地)上原いんの?
Really... That's good.
そっか…よかった
Daichi, I really like Ueha--
大ちゃん 私上原君のことが… 君のことカ...
I know.
(大地)分かってる
Then--
じゃあ
But doesn't he like that woman from this morning?
でもあいつは 朝のあの人のことが好きなんだろ?
Are you not giving up on him even though he likes someone else?
他に好きな人がいたら 菜緒はあいつのこと諦めんの?
I won't give up.
諦めないよ
Like I thought. So I'm not giving up either.
だろ? だったら俺も諦めない こった
But that's different than--
それとこれとは
It's the same.
(大地)同じだよ
Exactly the same.
Tai C
I'll wait for you patiently.
(大地)気長に待つ
Waiting is my specialty.
待つの得意だから
OK, see you later.
じゃあまたな
Nao.
菜緒
Marina.
まりな
This all feels kind of weird.
(菜緒) 何か変な感じなんだよね
It's like Daichi is different than the Daichi that I know.
私が知ってる 大ちゃんじゃないみたい
Well...
(まりな) うん
Either way, I don't think Daichi is different,
どっちも大ちゃんには 変わりないけど
but now he's just serious about you.
ただ菜緒に 本気になったってだけでしょ?
Mitsuishi says
(まりな)みつちゃんがね
Daichi will treat you way nicer than Uehara will.
上原君より大ちゃんのほうが 絶対優しくしてくれるってよ
That's not true!
そんなことないよ!
I mean, I know Daichi is nice and kind.
そりゃ大ちゃんが 優しいことは知ってるよ?
But Uehara is too.
けど上原君だって
He bought me a cake on Christmas,
クリスマスの日に ケーキ買ってきてくれたし
and he came back home during that blackout.
停電の日に 家帰ってきてくれたし
I'll admit he says mean things, and acts all big
確かに口が悪かったり 態度が偉そうだったり
and is cruel and grump and eats too much...
意地悪だったり不機嫌だったり 大食いだったり. \たつた
Huh? It sounds like there are more negatives--
(まりな)ん? 何か悪い部分のほうが多くない?
But... But even so
でも!それでも
after living with him for two months,
上原君が優しいことは
I can swear with confidence that he is nice and kind.
2ヶ月同居した私が 自信をもって保証する!
Really?
ん?
Then I've made up my mind.
決めた
Huh?
(菜緒)え?
I feel bad for Daichi,
大ちゃんには悪いけど
but I'm going to support you in your romance with Uehara.
私は菜緒と上原君の 恋を応援する
Charge ahead down the path you've chosen.
菜緒は自分の道を 突き進みなさい!
Marina...
(菜緒) まりな
So
(まりな)で!
where is that special Uehara? At work?
その肝心の上原君はどこ? バイト?
-Huh? -Where is he?
(菜緒)えっ (まりな)ん?
Well, you see...
それが …
Huh?
ん?
Darn you! With all the time you've been spending together,
もう! 散々一緒にいたのに
how come you didn't take action right away?
何でさっさと でさつで 行動に移さなかったの?
I can't help it. The mood has never been right.
だってそんな雰囲気 全然なかったし
Ah!
(菜緒)はっ!
You aren't trying hard enough!
努力が足りないの努力が!
How hard do you think Mitsuishi and I have been working at it?
私とみつちゃんが どれだけ頑張ってると思ってんの?
Unlike you, we're not living together, you know.
菜緒たちと違って一緒に 住んでるわけじゃないんだからね
Oh, you're right.
そっか
Uehara and I will be like you guys in the future.
これから私と上原君も そうなるんだ
You're a little late in realizing that.
気づくの遅っ...
Hmm...
うー つ ん
I've got to make sure our time together is well spent.
2人だけの時間は 大切にしなきゃ
Marina sure is smart.
やっぱいいこと言うよねえ まりなは
-I'm home. -Oh, hi, Yuri.
(百合)ただいま (菜緒)おかえりゆりりん!
-Huh? What's this? Tomorrow's lunch? -Uh-huh.
(百合)えー何?明日のお弁当? (菜緒) うん
That seems like a lot.
(百合)ちょっと量多くない?
Really?
(菜緒)そう?
Oh! You're making one for Uehara too, huh?
あっ久志の分も作ってんだ
Well, uh...
(菜緒)あついや
I just happened to make a lot, so I thought I'd make one for him too.
いっぱい作っちやったからさ ついでに
I see...
(EB) SI-AL
Uehara... Huh?
(菜緒)上原君 あれ?
Oh!
あっ!
What are you doing?
何してんだよ
We've only got a limited time.
(菜緒)時間は限られてるんだよ
Let's go!
ヘヘッ行こう!
-What's with you? -Hurry!
(上原)何だよ (菜緒)早く
What? Aren't you going to eat?
何?お前食わないの?
No.
(菜緒) うん
My chest feels so warm.
何か胸いっぱい
Heartburn? You must have eaten too much.
胸やけか? 食いすぎじゃねーの
You don't understand my feeling.
上原君には分かんないんだよ
No, I'm sorry.
(千春)ごめんなさい
-Abe. -This guy never learns.
(菜緒)あべっち (上原) こりねー奴
Nao!
(阿部)吉川
Oh, no! I was so enjoying our time alone.
まずい せっかくの2人っきりなのに
Nao, you won't believe this!
吉川聞いてくれよ~
Did you confess your love again?
(菜緒)あべっち べつ また告白したの?
-And got turned down. -Hey!
(上原) ...でフラれたと (菜緒)ちょっと
You'll never understand how I feel, Uehara.
上原に俺の気持ちなんか 分かんねーよ
Now, now. Cheer up, Abe.
(菜緒) まあまあ元気出して あべっち
-Here, you can have my lunch. -Really?
ほら私のお弁当あげるからさ (阿部)いいの?
-Uh-huh. Eat up. -All right!
(菜緒) うん食べていいよ (阿部)やった
Here you go.
(菜緒)はいどうぞ
-It looks delicious. Thank you! -No problem.
うまそういただきまーす (菜緒)はーい
-Huh? -Hey! What're you doing?
(阿訒えつ (菜緒)あっ!ちょっと上原君! つ!
-This won't be enough. -How much can you eat?
これだけじゃ足んねーし (菜緒)どんだけ食べんのよ
Enough for three.
3人前な
You'll make yourself sick if you eat that much.
そんな食べたらお腹壊すよ
I'm a growing boy, so don't worry.
育ち盛りだから心配ない
You skinny pig!
このヤセ大食いめ!
What?
仩原)は?
-Like I said, you're a skinny pig. -What are you talking about?
(菜緒)だからヤセ大食いだってば こつ 仩原)何それ?
Oh, yeah. Tomorrow's Saturday.
(菜緒)明日は土曜日かぁ
Oh! If you need lunch before your work tomorrow,
あっ上原君明日 バイト前にお昼食べるんだったら こつに
I'll make you one, OK?
お弁当作ってあげても いいけど?
You dummy. Tomorrow's a holiday. Our foundation day.
バ~カ 明日休みだぞ 創立記念日
-Really? -Uh-huh.
そうなの? 仩原) うん
Then the next day we'll meet is...
(菜緒) じゃあ次会える日は
-In three days. -You must be kidding...
(上原) しあさって (菜緒)そんな
This is the first time since we've been living together
(上原)吉川と同居してから 初めてかもな
that we won't see each other for two whole days.
丸2日会わないの
Two days... That's a long time.
(菜緒) 2日か長いな
It's not that long.
そうでもないだろ
Oh, by the way, what are your plans for the weekend?
あつちなみに 上原君の週末のご予定は?
Work.
バイト
Oh, yeah. That's right.
ハハ....だよねえ
Later.
じゃあな
Bye.
(菜緒) うん
I feel like I'm always saying goodbye to Uehara.
いつも上原君の 背中ばっか見てるな
He'd never text me.
メールなんか くれるわけないよね
Oh!
(菜緒)あつ
Yuri, your phone's ringing.
ゆりりん携帯鳴ってる
I know.
佰刽はーい
Thanks, Nao. They probably want me to work on my day off.
(百合)ありがとう菜緒ちゃん さては休日出勤のお誘いかぁ?
No, it's Uehara.
(菜緒) ううん上原君
Not again.
またか
I wish he'd call me.
(菜緒)いいな
-Here you go. -Huh?
(百合)はいこれ (菜緒)ん? し? はん
"Rolled cabbage, wieners,
“ロールキャベツウインナー クラムチャウダーハンバーグ,
cars, computers, tako-yaki, tai-yaki..."
"車パソコン たこ焼きたい焼き"
With these things, you can capture Uehara's heart for sure.
これで久志のハートを がっちりキャッチよ!
What? All these?
えつこんなにたくさん?
Well, I've known him for a long time.
まああいつとは 付き合い長いしね
Ahh. I wish I could return to that pure, innocent time.
あ~あ私も純粋だった あの頃に戻りたい
You mean it's not like that now?
今は違うの?
Life's all messed up now.
いろいろグチャグチャ
Well, it was always just me that was crazy in love.
まつ私だけが好きで 1人で空回ってんのは
That's never changed.
昔から変わんないけどね
What? You mean with Takuya?
えっ卓也さん?
That's right.
そう
I hate to admit it
悔しいけどさ
but he is really super handsome.
すっごくかっこいいんだもん
More than Uehara?
上原君より?
Yep. They're like chalk and cheese.
うん 月とスッポン
What? Uehara is chalk?
えっ上原君スッポン!? えつ
Yep. Oh, I know!
(百合) うん あつそうだ!
He's probably got an old photo album.
(百合)たぶんねあいつ 昔のアルバム持ってると思うんだ
Uehara will get angry if he finds out you've been in his room.
勝手に入ったら 上原君に怒られちゃうよ 女又
Then let him get angry. There's no need to worry about it.
(百合)怒らせとけばいいじゃん 気にしない気にしない
Wow! What a nice bed. Come have a seat on it, Nao.
うーわ!いいベッド! 菜緒ちゃんも座ってみ?
No, it's OK.
(菜緒) ううんやめとく
Don't be shy. Come on.
佰刽遠慮しないの はいはい
I'm not shy, just...
遠慮じゃなくて…
I think he doesn't mind if you do that, Yuri.
そういうのはゆりりんだから 許されるんだと思う
-Nao. -Excuse me.
菜緒ちゃん (菜緒)ごめん
I've got to do some shopping.
ちょっと買い物行かなくちゃだった いってきます
Ah! Wait! Hold on a sec, Nao.
佰刽あつちょっと待って 菜緒ちゃん
I wonder... what Uehara's doing now.
(菜緒)何してるかな上原君
-Ah! I'm sorry. -No. It's my fault.
(百合)ああごめんなさい (阿部)いやこちらこそ
Hey, you were talking with Uehara the other day. You're that...
ってああ! この前上原と話してた
pretty woman.
きれいな人
Are you a friend of Uehara's?
久志の知り合い?
Here you are!
いっせい (一星)へいお待ち!
It looks delicious! Yum!
佰合)おいしそ~! うん
Come here...
(一星)ちょっとお前
You've already got a new girlfriend?
お前もう 新しい彼女できたのか?
No...
いや
but I'm getting my courage up to ask her out.
これから勇気をもって 告白します
Oh, I see.
85そうか の
-Dad, one soft boiled egg! -Here you go!
親父味玉! (徹平)はいよ
Eat up. It'll give you courage. On the house.
(一星)景気づけに食っとけ おごりだ
Thank you, my teacher.
(阿部)師匠 (一星)食っとけ )ノ
-So... -Yes?
さい では 合部 百阿
Are you friends with Nao too?
阿部君は 菜緒ちゃんとも仲いいの?
For sure. We're good friends.
(阿部)もう めちゃめちゃ知り合いです
Really?
本当に!?
Then from your point of view, what do you think of those two?
じゃあ阿部君から見て あの2人ってどう?
What do I think? I think they make a good couple.
どうって いい感じじゃないですか
That's because
tha...
Nao's working so hard at it, don't you think?
菜緒ちゃんが 頑張ってるからでしょ?
Not really...
いや…
-Thank you! -No problem
(阿部)いただきまーす (菜緒)はーい
-Hey! What're you doing? -This won't be enough.
(菜緒)あっ!ちょっと上原君 (上原) これだけじゃ足んねーし
-How much can you eat? -Enough for three.
(菜緒)どんだけ食べんのよ (上原) 3人前な
I think that Uehara likes Nao too.
俺上原も吉川のこと 好きだと思いますよ
What? You think so?
えっそうなの!?
You think so?
(徹平)そうなの?
See you later, guys.
じゃあなお疲れ
See you.
(雄平·駿介)お疲れさまです
-Nao. -Daichi.
(大地)菜緒! (菜緒)大ちゃん
Ah! It's OK. I can carry those.
えつめつ大丈夫 私持てるから
You sure bought a lot. Have you been worrying over Uehara?
随分買い込んだな 貝い込んたな 上原のことで悶々としてた?
No, not really...
いや別に…
It's so easy to tell what you're thinking.
本当菜緒は分かりやすいな
You think so?
そうかな
But that's what I like about you.
それがいいとこだけど
Wait up.
ちょっと待って
Daichi.
(菜緒)大ちゃん
Ah! Uehara.
あっ上原君
Nao! Uehara!
(百合)菜緒ちゃん 久志
-Yuri! Abe? -Yo!
(菜緒)ゆりりんあべっち? (阿部)オッス
You came back?
(百合)久志帰ってきたんだ
I just happened to be passing by, that's all... Bye.
たまたま通りかかっただけだよ じゃあな
I have an idea! Since Nao's friends are all here,
よし!今日は菜緒ちゃんの お友達も集まってくれたことだし
today we're going to have a great big party!
今日はパーッと 盛り上がりましよ!
-Really? All right! -Come on.
(阿部)マジで!?よっしゃ! (百合)はいはい
What the hell are you thinking?
仩原) お前勝手に何言ってんだよ
If you're worried, then you'll just have to join us, won't you?
心配ならあんたも 来るしかないんじゃない?
What?
仩原)はあ?
Come on, you two. Let's go.
(百合) 2人とも行こう行こう
-Huh? -Come on. This way.
休地)えっ (百合)はいはい…どうぞ.
Since you insisted, we came.
お言葉に甘えて 来ちゃいました~
-Oh! Welcome! -Come on in!
(菜緒)あーいらっしゃい 佰合)入って入って して あ入
-Thanks for inviting us. -No problem.
お邪魔しまーす (菜緒)はーい
We'll start by using these.
とりあえずあるだけ使おつか
Go ahead.
はい
Oh, OK.
あーはい
Thanks, Mitsuishi.
(菜緒)みつちゃんありがとう (チャイム)
Domino's Pizza.
(配達員) ドミソピザっす
Hey, the pizza's here.
(百合)あーピザ来たよ
Hey, handsome. You too, handsome. Give me a hand.
はいイケメン はいイケメン手伝って
-Me too? -Did you hear? I'm handsome.
(大地)俺もっすか? (25)聞いた?イケメン
-What? -She said he's handsome.
まりな)えっ何? (菜緒)イケメンだって
That'll go to his head for sure.
(まりな)調子乗っちゃうから
Wow, I never thought you and Uehara were living together, Nao.
いやーまさか 吉川と上原が同居してたなんて
It's like you've got a head start.
先越されたって感じだな
You know, Abe, you've got to find yourself a girlfriend first.
あのほらまず あべっちは彼女を見つけなよ
That's right.
(菜緒)そうだよ
Right now, Yuri and I are really getting along.
俺今ゆりりんと すっげーいい感じでさ
I think I'm going to confess my love to her today.
今日告白しようと思ってる
What are you thinking? Yuri's married, you know.
は?何言ってんの ゆりりん結婚してるよ
Anyway, forget that. Put out the plates.
そんなのいいから早く お皿並べて
What? What?
えつえつ!?
No, no. You're mistaken.
いやいや何かの間違いでしよ
No, I'm not mistaken at all.
全然間違ってないから フフッ
-Really? You're not? -Never mind, Abe.
間違ってない? (菜緒)ハハ…ドンマイあべつち
-Never mind? -Never mind!
ドンマイ? (まりな) ドンマイ!
OK, looks like we're ready. Shall we?
じゃあ準備もできたことだし 食べよっか!
-Uh-huh. One, two... -Let's eat!
(菜緒) うんせ~の (一同)いただきま~す!
This looks delicious.
(菜緒)おいしそ~
This is all on me today, so eat all you want.
(百合)今日は私のおごりよ! じゃんじゃん食べてね
Thank you!
(光石)ありがとうございます
I'm going to eat until I burst! Give me that fried chicken.
(阿部)もう俺食いまくる! から揚げも~らい
I don't know where to start.
(光石)すげえ迷うな
Yum! This potato salad is delicious, Nao.
(まりな) うーん! このポテサラおいしいよ菜緒
Really? But I always start with--
えっ!?でも一番最初は
This, right?
(大地) これだろ?
-Uh-huh. -Here.
(菜緒) うん (大地)はい
Thank you.
(菜緒)ありがとう
You dummy! You can't eat just meat.
(百合)あんた 肉だけ取んじゃないわよ
I can eat whatever I like.
(上原)何食おうと 俺の勝手だろうが
Hey.
おい
Here.
佰刽はい
No meat for you until you eat this.
これ食べ終えるまで肉禁止
-Oh, Abe! -Yes?
佰合)あーあべっち! -あべつ (阿部)はい 百︶
Can you get me another drink?
(百合)飲み物お代わり よろしく~
She's already made me her gofer.
(阿部) 俺もうパシリにされてるよ
What flavor do you want, Yuri?
ゆりりん何味?
Orange.
佰合)オレンジ
OK.
はーい
Nao, go get some dressing.
仩原) 吉川ドレッシング持ってきて
Go get it yourself.
(菜緒) 自分で持ってきなよ
Thank you.
佰刽はいありがとう
Ahh!
あー!
Dammit. Who let her drink alcohol?
仩原) ったく誰だ つたくー あいつに酒飲ませたの
Don't touch me. It was you?
触んなよ お前かよ
Yeah,
いやだって…ゆりりんが こつ
but I didn't know she'd end up like that.
あんなふうになるな 知らなかったし
Aah!
佰合)あ~ !
Abe, I found you!
あべっちみーつけ べつ
Get over here.
ちょっとこっち来て
-Let's kiss. -Really? We can?
チューしよ? (阿部)えっ!?いいの?
Yes--
やった…イッテ! つに
You're so cruel to me, Uehara.
上原俺に冷たすぎ!
Wait! Wait! Hold on!
(光石) ちよ…ちょっと待った!
Marina, uh...
(光石) まりなあの
Wait! Disappear, Mitsuishi!
(まりな)ちょっと... みつちゃん消えて
-Ow! You totally kicked me. -Out of the way!
痛いマジ蹴りは 佰合) う-邪魔
-Ah! No, I couldn't. -Daichi!
(大地)あーちょっと俺は困ります (菜緒)大ちゃん!
Hey, Yuri!
(上原)おい百合
Oh! That's mine.
佰合)あっ私のだ
OK, OK.
はいは~い
Hello?
もしも~し
I don't have anything to do with him anymore.
もう関係ないですから
Don't you see?
だから!
I'm divorcing Takuya!
私卓也と 別れることにしたんです
Fine. Do what you like.
(百合)どうぞご自由に
Sorry about that. You young kids enjoy yourselves.
ごめんね あとは若者で楽しんで
The old person will now go get depressed.
年寄りはここいらで ドロンします
-I'll need your room, Nao. -Hey, Yuri. Wait!
菜緒ちゃん部屋借りるね (上原)おい百合待てよ
I see...
まりな)そっか... ゆりりんもいろいろあるんだね
Yeah.
(菜緒) うん
-OK, bye. See you. -Yeah, see you.
まりな)あつじゃあまたね (菜緒) うんまたね
-Thanks for coming. -No problem.
ありがとう まりな)はい
Ahh, adults sure do have it hard.
あ~あ大人って大変だな
I've got a bruise here for sure.
(光石)絶対アザだよ
Yuri says she wants to talk to you.
(上原)百合 お前と話したいってよ
OK.
うん
It's Nao. Can I come in?
(菜緒)菜緒です 入っても大丈夫?
Uh-huh.
うん
Sorry. I drank too much again.
ごめんね また飲みすぎちゃつた
Who was that call from?
さっきの電話
It was Takuya's...
卓也のね大学時代の彼女
Even since they broke up, they've been seeing each other as friends.
別れてからも ずっと友達関係続いてて
He even lied to me to go and see her in the evening.
私にウソついてまで その彼女と夜会ってんだよね
Ahh. I really hate myself.
あ~あ やんなっちゃつたなあ よつ
I was always chasing after him.
私ばっか好き好き騒いで
I must seem like a fool.
バカみたいだと思わない?
I don't think so.
そうかな?
Really?
佰合)え?
I think when you like someone, you turn into a kind of fool.
バカになっちやうんじゃないかな? 好きになると
That person is always on your mind.
いつもその人のことばっか 考えちゃつて
You get upset over silly things and worry about him for no reason.
つまらないこと気にして 1人で悶々としちゃつて
But when you're with him, you're incredibly happy.
(菜緒)でもその人に会えたら すっごいうれしくて
All your troubles and worries are instantly swept away.
モヤモヤも全部 パーツて吹っ飛んじゃうみたいに
Nao.
菜緒ちゃん
Oh, uh...
あついや…
Anyway, it's OK to be a fool, Yuri.
とにかくゆりりんは バカでいいってこと
Huh?
佰刽ん?
Uh, I don't mean that kind of thing.
あついや そういうことじゃなくて
Oh... I don't know how to put it.
ハァ…うまく言えない
Thank you, Nao.
ありがとう菜緒ちゃん
Sure.
うん
Is Yuri all right?
(上原)百合大丈夫か?
-Yeah, maybe. -"Maybe"?
(菜緒) うんたぶん (上原) "たぶん”って
If you're that worried about her, you go talk to her.
そんなに心配なら お前が行けば?
This has nothing to do with you.
あんたに関係ないだろ
Excuse me. Sorry to interrupt you guys.
(阿部)あの… お取り込み中すいません
-What?
(大地,上原)何?
My stomach hurts.
俺腹痛い
-Huh?
(3人)はあ!?
What's with that guy?
何なんだよあいつは
I think he overate.
(菜緒) たぶん食べすぎだと思う
He'll be fine. He took medicine.
薬あげたから 大丈夫だと思うけど
So where the heck am I supposed to sleep?
ったく俺は つに どこで寝ればいいんだよ
Oh... Yuri's using my room too.
あっ私もゆりりんに 部屋貸しちゃつたし やった
We'll just have to sleep here tonight.
今日ここで寝るしかないかもね
You two... You're going to sleep here together?
お前ら今日2人で ここで寝るつもりか?
You're going to miss the last train.
もう終電なくなりますよ
-I'm staying over tonight. -Huh?
俺今日泊まるから (菜緒)えっ
-Hey, you crashed into me on purpose. -No, it was just an accident.
お前わざとやったろ (上原)たまたまっすよ
-Hey! What are you doing? -Oh, sorry. I didn't see you.
あっちよっ…何するんすか!? (大地)ああ悪い見えなかった
So much happened that I can't sleep now.
何かいろいろあって 眠くなくなっちゃつたなあ
Then how about something to eat?
(上原) じゃあこれでも食う?
Oh! You're awake, Uehara?
あっ上原君起きてたんだ
Yeah.
仩原) うん
Huh? What's that?
(菜緒)ん?何それ
The one thing we both agree on.
俺とお前といえば これだろ こつ
You got that for me?
どうして?
No, I just thought you might want to have one.
いや別に お前食いたいかと思って
You mean you came here to see me today?
今日は私に 会いに来てくれたってこと?
Huh? What're you talking about?
は?何言ってんだ?
Oh, nothing. Let's eat.
ううん何でもない 食べよ ベ
-Thank you. -Yeah, sure.
いただきます (上原)いただきます
Yum! Dang, this is good.
う~んうめ~
But a little warm.
けどぬる~
So you think of milk pudding when you think of me, huh?
私と上原君といえば 牛乳プリンか
What are all the smiles about?
何1人で笑ってんだよ
Even though we've only been together for a short time,
一緒にいるのは まだまだ短いけど
we've already got this in common.
私たちには これがあるもんね!
Huh?
(EPT)
Yum!
(菜緒) う~ん!
Today, this pudding is better than usual.
今日のプリンは一段とおいしい! フフフ
That doesn't make sense.
意味が分からん
Because this is full of your kindness.
上原君の優しさが 詰まってるよ
I told you, I just happened to be passing by.
だから! たまたま通っただけだっつーの こまたま週つたた
Really?
ふー ん
Yeah, really.
(上原) "ふーん"じゃねーよ (菜緒)フフッ
You going to eat that? I'll have it.
(上原)食うなそれ つな 俺が食う
-You can't have it. -Huh? Hey...
(菜緒)あげない (上原)え?おい
-Look. -Huh?
(菜緒)ん? (上原)えっ えつ んえ
Yum! This is so good.
(菜緒)ん-おいしい
Yum. Pretty good, isn't it?
(菜緒)んーフフッ おいしそうでしょ
Ahh, what fine weather again today. I'm feeling fine too.
(阿部)あー今日もいい天気 俺も絶好調
OK, then get out right now.
仩原)よーし じゃあ今すぐ帰れ
Huh? Ah! Oh!
え…おつあつ つめつ おっ! お!
Jeez, you sure are cold to me.
何だよ冷たいな
Oops!
(阿部)お…おお
Ahh, now I'm all cold.
(HR) as VA
Hey, you're living at your house, right? Let's go back together.
なあ今実家なんだろ? 一緒に帰ろうぜ
I want to talk to you about something.
ちょっと話したいことある
Yeah, sure.
いいつすけど
What did you want to talk about?
(上原)何すか話って
You like Yuri, don't you?
(大地)お前百合さんのこと 好きなんだろ
That's none of your business--
仩原) だからあんたには関係ない
I really don't care at all who you like.
(大地)俺お前が誰が好きとか そういうの全く興味ねえけど
But I will never stand for Nao to get hurt by you.
菜緒が傷つくのだけは 見てらんねえんだよ
She and I aren't like that.
俺とあいつは そういうんじゃないっすから
Then why the hell...
(大地)だったら!
Why don't you tell her that?
菜緒にもはっきり そう伝えろよ
Don't you dare take this lightly.
中途半端な態度 とってんじゃねーぞ
I've told Nao that I like her.
俺菜緒に好きだって 伝えたから
Nice to meet you. Thank you for always looking after my brother.
初めまして いつも弟がお世話になってます
Your brother?
弟?
I'm Uehara's older brother, Takuya.
久志の兄の上原卓也です
Older brother...
兄...
Oh! You're Uehara's big brother?
はっ!上原君のお兄さん?